Guide to the W. D. Davies papers, 1911-2007 UA.29.02.0016
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2014.0065, 1911-2007; 2
  - Books, 5
    - Jews, Greeks and Christians: Religious Cultures in Late Antiquity: essays in honor of William David Davies, 1976 (Box 65)
    - John, 1999 (Box 68)
      Author: D. Moody Smith; Publisher: Abingdon Press; Place of Publication: Nashville; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription, Dedication
    - Journal for the Study of the New Testament: Issue 37, 1989 (Box 65)
      Author: N/A; Publisher: Sheffield Academic Press; Place of Publication: England; Paperback; Language: English; Special edition edited by Cristopher Tucker; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - Judaism Practice and Belief 63 BCE - 66 CE (Box 66)
      Author: E.P. Sanders; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription, Dedication
    - Justice and Mercy (Box 75)
      Author: Reinhold Niebuhr; Language: English
    - La Reduction Du Pluriel Au Singulier Dans L'Evangile et La Premiere Lettre De Jean (Box 73)
      Author: F.M. Braun; Language: French
    - L'Enfance Du Christianisme, 1997 (Box 68)
      Author: Etienne Trocmé; Paperback; Language: French; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - L'Evangile Selon Saint Marc, 2000 (Box 70)
      Author: Etienne Trocmé; Place of Publication: Paris; Paperback; Language: French
    - L'Evangile, hier et aujourd' hui, 1968 (Box 70)
      Author: Franz-J. Leenhardt; Place of Publication: Paris; Paperback; Language: French
    - Llafar, 1953 (Box 72)
      Author: Aneirin Talfan Davies; Publisher: Aberystwyth Press; Place of Publication: Aberystwyth; Paperback; Language: Welsh
    - Love and the Messianic Age (Box 66)
      Author: P.P. Levertoff; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - MacMillan's Progressive German Course: First Year, 1923 (Box 68)
      Author: G. Eugene Fasnacht; Publisher: Macmillan and Co., LTD; Place of Publication: London; Hardcover; Language: English/German; Significance to W.D. Davies: Annotated
    - Making Sense of New Testament Theology: Modern Problems and Prospects, 1995 (Box 68)
      Author: A.K.M. Adam; Publisher: Mercer University Press; Place of Publication: Georgia; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - The Man Who was Shakespeare, 1995 (Box 70)
      Author: Charlton Ogburn; Publisher: EPM Publishing; Place of Publication: Virginia; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Mary: Glimpses of the Mother of Jesus, 1995 (Box 73)
      Author: Beverly Roberts Gaventa; Publisher: University of South Carolina Press; Place of Publication: Columbia; Hardcover; Language: English
    - Matthew In History: Interpretation Influence and Effects, 1994 (Box 71)
      Author: Ulrich Luz; Publisher: Fortress Press; Place of Publication: Minneapolis; Paperback; Language: English
    - The Messianic Idea and Judaism and Other Essays on Jewish Spirituality, 1971 (Box 68)
      Author: Gersholm Scholem; Publisher: Schocken Books; Place of Publication: Ne York; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Annotated
    - The Mishnah, 1933 (Box 64)
      Author: Herbert Danby; Publisher: Oxford University Press; Place of Publication: London; Hardcover; Language: English; First Edition; Significance to W.D. Davies: Annotated
    - Modern Critical Views: Gershom Scholem, 1987 (Box 73)
      Author: Harold Bloom; Publisher: Chelsea House Publishing; Place of Publication: United States; Hardcover; Language: English
    - Mormons and Jews: Early Mormon Theologices of Israel, 1992 (Box 70)
      Author: Steven Epperson; Publisher: Signature Books; Place of Publication: Salt Lake City, Utah; Paperback; Language: English
    - My Name is Asher Lev, 1972 (Box 68)
      Author: Chaim Potok; Publisher: The Chaucer Press; Place of Publication: Great Britain; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Neb, 1985 (Box 72)
      Author: R.S. Thomas; Publisher: Gwynedd Press; Paperback; Language: Welsh; First Edition
    - Neotestamentica et Patristica, 1962 (Box 65)
      Author: Unknown; Publisher: EJ Brill; Place of Publication: Netherlands; Hardcover; Language: Dutch, English, French; Volume six; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - The New Creation: University Sermons, 1971 (Box 63)
    - The New English Bible with the Apocrypha, 1970 (Box 75)
      Publisher: Oxford University Press and Cambridge University Press; Place of Publication: Oxford; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Davies involved in translation
    - The New Testament Age: Essays in Honor of Bo Reicke, 1984 (Box 65)
      Author: William Weinrich; Publisher: Mercer University Press; Place of Publication: Macon, Georgia; Hardcover; Language: Many languages; 2 volumes; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - New Testament and Psalms (Box 74)
      Author: The Gideons; Language: English, French
    - The New Testament and Rabbinic Judaism, 1956 (Box 66)
      Author: David Daube; Publisher: The Athlone Press; Place of Publication: London; Hardcover; Language: English
    - New Testament Judaism: Collected Works of David Daube, 2000 (Box 73)
      Author: Calum Carmichael; Publisher: Robbins Collections Publications; Place of Publication: Berkeley, California; Hardcover; Language: English
    - New Testament Theology: The Theology of the Gospel of John, 1995 (Box 66)
      Author: D. Moody Smith; Publisher: Cambridge University Press; Place of Publication: New York; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Nine Mysteries (Box 75)
      Author: Reynolds Price; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Nouveau Testament et Psaumes, 1963 (Box 66)
      Author: Louis Segond; Publisher: Alliance Biblique Universalle; Place of Publication: Netherlands; Hardcover; Language: French; Translated by Louis Segond; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - O Gopa Bryn Nebo, 1967 (Box 72)
      Author: Atgofion Nantlais; Publisher: Gomer Press; Place of Publication: Llandysul; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - On Jews and Judaism in Crisis (Box 75)
      Author: Gersholm Scholem; Language: English
    - On the Eve of the Millennium, 1994 (Box 68)
      Author: Connor Cruise O'Brien; Publisher: House of Anansi Press; Place of Publication: Ontario; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Opposition to Paul in Jewish Christianity (Box 66)
      Author: Gerd Luedemann; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Dedication
    - The Oxford Dictionary of the Christian Church, 1957 (Box 71)
      Author: F.L. Cross; Publisher: Oxford University Press; Place of Publication: Great Britain; Hardcover; Language: English
    - Paul, 1991 (Box 73)
      Author: E.P. Sanders; Publisher: Oxford University Press; Place of Publication: New York; Paperback; Language: English
    - Paul and Rabbinic Judaism, 1977 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: S.P.C.K. London; Place of Publication: London; Paperback; Language: English; Third edition, second impression; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - Paul and Rabbinic Judaism, 1980 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Fortress Press; Paperback; Language: English; Fourth edition; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - Paul and Rabbinic Judaism, 1998 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Sigler Press; Hardcover; Language: English; 50th Anniversary, unopened copy in plastic wrap; Significance to W.D. Davies: Unopened Copy
    - Paul and Rabbinic Judaism, 1948 (Box 63)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: University Press; Place of Publication: Cambridge; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored, Annotated
    - Paul and Rabbinic Judaism: Some Rabbinic Elements in Pauline Theology, 1948 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: S.P.C.K. London; Hardcover; Language: English; includes errata slip; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - Paul and Rabbinic Judaism: Some Rabbinic Elements in Pauline Theology, 1970 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: S.P.C.K. London; Place of Publication: London; Paperback; Language: English; Third edition; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - Paul and Rabbinic Judaism: Some Rabbinic Elements in Pauline Theology (Revised Edition), 1967 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Harper Torchbooks, Harper and Row; Place of Publication: New York; Paperback; Language: English; Revised; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - Paul and Rabbinic Judaism: Some Rabbinic Elements in Pauline Theology (Revised Edition), 1998 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Sigler Press; Place of Publication: Pennsylvania; Paperback; Language: English; 50th Anniversary; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - Paul and the Scriptures of Israel, 1993 (Box 65)
      Author: Edited by Craig A. Evans and James A. Sanders; Publisher: JSOT Press; Place of Publication: England; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - Paulus und das Judentum, 1983 (Box 66)
      Author: Gerd Ludemann; Publisher: Kaiser Verlag Munchen; Place of Publication: Germany; Paperback; Language: German; Significance to W.D. Davies: Dedication/Inscription
    - Peake's Commentary on the Bible, 1962 (Box 67)
      Author: Matthew Black and H. H. Rowley; Publisher: Thomas Nelson ad Sons LTD; Place of Publication: Edinburgh; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor, Annotated
    - The People of the Dead Sea Scrolls (Box 75)
      Author: John Marco Allegro; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Perlau Bro Talylly Chall, 1993 (Box 69)
      Author: Brenda M James; Publisher: Cyhoeddiadau Modern Cymreig Cyf.; Place of Publication: Gwynedd, Wales; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Perspectives on New Testament Ethics: Essays in Honor of Dan O. Via, 1996 (Box 65)
      Author: Edited by Perry V Kea and A.K.M. Adam; Publisher: National Association of Baptist Professors of Religion; Place of Publication: Macon, Georgia; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - Poetry of the World at Christmas, 1996 (Box 70)
      Author: Kenneth Cragg; Publisher: New Millennium Publishing; Place of Publication: Durham, North Carolina; Paperback; Language: English
    - Pour comprendre le Sermon sur la Montagne, 1970 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Paperback; Language: French; translated by Elaine Mac Gaw; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - Prayer in the New Testament, 1995 (Box 71)
      Author: Oscar Cullmann; Publisher: Fortress Press; Place of Publication: Minneapolis; Paperback; Language: English; First North American edition
    - Proceedings of the American Academy for Jewish Research, 1993-1996 (Box 76)
      Author: Nahum M. Sarna (Ed); Publisher: Ben-Zvi Printing Enterprises LTD.,; Place of Publication: Jerusalem; Hardcover; Language: English; Postcard inserted
    - Proceedings of the British Academy, 1991-1999 (Box 76)
      Author: Dr. Marjorie Chibnall (Ed); Publisher: Oxford University Press; Place of Publication: New York; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Corresponding Member of the British Academy
    - The Prophet Joseph Smith's Testimony (Box 74)
      Author: The Church of Jesus Christ of the Latter-day Saints; Language: English
    - The Prophets (Box 66)
      Author: Abraham J. Heschel; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Putting Body & Soul Together: Essays in Honor of Robin Scroggs, 1997 (Box 73)
      Author: Virginia Wiles, Alexandra Brown and Graydon F. Snyder; Publisher: Trinity Press International; Place of Publication: Valley Forge, Pennsylvania; Paperback; Language: English
    - A Rabbinic Anthology, 1938 (Box 64)
      Author: C.G. Montefiore and H. Loewe; Publisher: Macmillan and Co., LTD; Place of Publication: London; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Annotated
    - Racial Prejudice in Imperial Rome, 1966 (Box 68)
      Author: A.N. Sherwin-White; Publisher: Cambridge University Press; Place of Publication: London; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Annotated
    - A Radical Jew: Paul and the Politics of Identity, 1994 (Box 66)
      Author: Daniel Boyarin; Publisher: University of California Press; Place of Publication: Berkeley; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Dedication
    - Real Presences, 1989 (Box 68)
      Author: George Steiner; Publisher: The University of Chicago Press; Place of Publication: Chicago; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Annotated
    - The Recollections of R. Taylor Cole, 1983 (Box 75)
      Author: R. Taylor Cole; Publisher: Duke University Press; Place of Publication: Durham; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - "Reflections on Territory in Judaism," by W. D. Davies, from Sha'arei Talmon, 1992 (Box 74)
      Author: Michael Fishbane and Emmanuel Tov; Publisher: Eisenbrauns; Place of Publication: Winona Lake, Indiana; Offprint; Language: English
    - Reflections on Mormonism; Judaeo-Christian Parallels, 1978 (Box 67)
      Author: Truman G. Madsen; Publisher: Religious Studies Center Brigham Young University; Place of Publication: Salt Lake City, Utah; Hardcover; Language: English; Second printing 1980; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - Reinhold Niebuhr: A Biography, 1985 (Box 75)
      Author: Richard Wightman Fox; Publisher: Pantheon Books; Place of Publication: New York; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Annotated
    - The Religion and Mythology of the Greeks, 1961 (Box 70)
      Author: W.K.C. Guthrie; Publisher: Cambridge University Press; Place of Publication: Great Britain; Paperback; Language: English
    - Remembering Reinhold Niebuhr: Letters of Reinhold and Ursula M. Niebuhr, 1991 (Box 75)
      Author: Edited by Ursula M. Niebuhr; Publisher: Harper San Francisco; Place of Publication: New York; Hardcover; Language: English
    - Renewing the Judeo-Christian Wellsprings, 1987 (Box 65)
      Author: Dr. Val Ambrose Mcinnes; Publisher: Crossroad Publishing Co; Place of Publication: New York; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor, Inscription
    - Renewing the Judeo-Christian Wellsprings (Box 65)
      Author: Dr. Val Ambrose Mcinnes; Publisher: Crossroad Publishing Co; Place of Publication: New York; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - Reopening the World: Reading Mark as Theology in the Context of Early Judaism, 2002 (Box 74)
      Author: Sabin, Marie Noonan; Publisher: Oxford University Press; Place of Publication: New York; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription (to his daughter Rachel M. Davies).
    - The Resonance of Grace, 1984 (Box 66)
      Author: James Newcomer; Publisher: Latitudes Press; Place of Publication: Texas; paperback; Language: English; First edition paperback; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - The Revised Hagada (Box 64)
      Author: A. A. Green; Publisher: Wertheimer, Lea & Co.; Place of Publication: London; Hardcover; Language: English, Hebrew; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription, Annotated
    - Rewriting the Bible: Land and Covenant in Postbiblical Jewish Literature, 1994 (Box 66)
      Author: Betset Halpern-Amaru; Publisher: Trinity Press International; Place of Publication: Valley Forge, Pennsylvania; paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Reviewed, Quote on back cover
    - The Roots of a Radical, 1980 (Box 66)
      Author: John A.T. Robinson; Publisher: SCM Press; Place of Publication: London; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription, Annotated
    - The Satanizing of the Jews: Origin and Development of Mystical Anti-Semitism, 1992 (Box 68)
      Author: Joel Carmichael; Publisher: Fromm International Publishing; Place of Publication: New York; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Annotated
    - Saunders Lewis: El Feddwl A'I Waith, 1950 (Box 69)
      Author: Pennar Davies; Publisher: Wasg Gee press; Hardcover; Place of Publication: Denbigh, Wales; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Scottish Journal of Theology, 1991 (Box 67)
      Author: Unknown; Publisher: T&T Clark Limited; Place of Publication: Edinburgh; Paperback; Language: English; Scottish Journal of Theology volume 44; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - The Second Epistle to the Corinthians, 1993 (Box 73)
      Author: Nigel Watson; Publisher: Epworth Press; Place of Publication: Minneapolis; Paperback; Language: English
    - Septuaginta: Vol I, 1935 (Box 70)
      Author: Alfred Rahlfs; Place of Publication: Stuttgart; Hardcover; Language: English, German, Hebrew
    - Septuaginta: Vol II, 1935 (Box 70)
    - The Sermon on the Mount, 1966 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Cambridge University Press; Place of Publication: London; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - The Sermon on the Mount (Japanese Translation), 1991 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Paperback; Language: Japanese; translated by Kyo Bun Kwan; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - The Setting of the Sermon on the Mount, 1966 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Cambridge University Press; Place of Publication: London; Paperback; Language: English; Reprint of 1963; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - The Setting of the Sermon on the Mount, 1989 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Scholars Press; Place of Publication: Brown University; Hardcover; Language: English; Brown Judaic Studies Number 186; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - The Setting of the Sermon on the Mount (Box 63)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Cambridge University Press; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - The Setting of the Sermon on the Mount, 1966 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Cambridge University Press; Hardcover; Language: English; Reprint of 1963; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - Sha'arei Talmon, 1992 (Box 65)
      Author: Edited by Emanuel Tov and Michael Fishbane; Publisher: Eisenbrauns; Place of Publication: Indiana; Hardcover; Language: Multiple Languages; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - Shakespeare's Self-Portrait, 1992 (Box 66)
      Author: Charlton Ogburn; Publisher: Oxenford Press; Place of Publication: Northampton, MA; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - The Silence of Angels, 1995 (Box 73)
      Author: Dale C. Allison Jr; Publisher: Trinity Press International; Place of Publication: Valley Forge, Pennsylvania; Paperback; Language: English
    - Specimens towards A New Translation of the Bible, 1958 (Box 73)
      Author: Unknown; No publisher or place of publication listed; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Early work on the New English Bible translation with C.H. Dodd
    - Sprung Time: Seasons of the Christian Year, 1980 (Box 66)
      Author: Robert G. Hammerton-Kelly; Publisher: The Upper Room; Place of Publication: Tennessee; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Storm from Paradise: The Politics of Jewish Memory, 1992 (Box 68)
      Author: Jonathan Boyarin; Publisher: University of Minnesota Press; Place of Publication: Minneapolis; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Studies in Paul and John, 1990 (Box 65)
      Author: Edited by Robert T. Fortna and Beverly R. Gaventa; Publisher: Abingdon Press; Place of Publication: Nashville, Tennessee; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - The Territorial Dimension of Judaism, 1982 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: University of California Press; Place of Publication: Los Angeles, California; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - The Territorial Dimension of Judaism, 1982 (Box 68)
    - The Territorial Dimension of Judaism (Japanese Edition), 1992 (Box 62)
    - The Territorial Dimensions of Judaism: With a Symposium and Further Reflections, 1991 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Augsburg Fortress; Place of Publication: Minneapolis; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - The Theme of Jewish Persecution of Christians in the Gospel According to St Matthew, 1967 (Box 73)
      Author: Douglas R. A. Hare; Publisher: Cambridge University Press; Place of Publication: Great Britain; Hardcover; Language: English
    - The Time It Is: A Play about Jesus, 1982 (Box 66)
      Author: Dan Otto Via; Publisher: University Press of America; Place of Publication: Washington DC; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Torah in the Messianic Age and/or the Age to Come, 1952 (Box 63)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Society of Biblical Literature; Place of Publication: Philadelphia; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - Triads and Trinity, 1996 (Box 66)
      Author: J Gwyn Griffiths; Publisher: University of Wales Press; Place of Publication: Cardiff; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Ty'nywern fy leuenctyd (Box 72)
      Author: William Anthony Davies; Publisher: Jones and Mainwaring; Place of Publication: Ammanford, Wales; Paperback; Language: Welsh
    - Types of Philosophy, 1929 (Box 64)
      Author: William Ernest Hocking; Publisher: The Scribner Press; Place of Publication: United States; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription, Annotated
    - Un Er Mwyn Y Byd, 1998 (Box 69)
      Author: Noel A. Davies; Publisher: John Penri Press; Place of Publication: Swansea; Paperback; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Union Theological Seminary (Box 75)
    - University of Wales College of Cardiff Honorary Fellows and Fellows, 1993 (Box 76)
      Author: Unknown; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Davies was named an honorary fellow.
    - Walter Benjamin: The Story of a Friendship, 1975 (Box 75)
      Author: Gershom Scholem; Translator: Harry Zohn; Publisher: Jewish Publication Society of America; Place of Publication, Philadelphia; Hardcover; Language: English
    - The Way We See Things Now, 1993 (Box 66)
      Author: Robert Anderson, Harry Wardlaw, Nigel Watson; Publisher: Joint Board of Christian Education; Place of Publication: Melbourne; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - What are they saying about Matthew's Sermon on the Mount?, 1982 (Box 68)
      Author: Warren Carter; Publisher: Paulist Press; Place of Publication: New York; Paperback; Language:; Significance to W.D. Davies: Cited in Introduction
    - What Decided Christianity: Event and Experience in the New Testament, 1989 (Box 68)
      Author: Kenneth Craig; Publisher: Churchman Publishing; Place of Publication: Great Britain; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Who is Man?, 1965 (Box 68)
      Author: Abraham Heschel; Publisher: Stanford University Press; Place of Publication: Stanford; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Annotated
    - William Morgan and his Bible, 1988 (Box 73)
      Author: Isaac Thomas; Publisher: University of Wales Press; Place of Publication: Cardiff; Paperback; Language: English
    - The Works of Flavius Josephus (Box 64)